<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Marketing on Polis Paralela</title>
    <link>/thinks/categories/digital-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Marketing on Polis Paralela</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:30:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/thinks/categories/digital-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping Cade Street Nursery to Grow</title>
      <link>/thinks/helping-cade-street-nursery-to-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 15:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/helping-cade-street-nursery-to-grow/</guid>
      <description>What we did • Digital Marketing
• Social Media
• Paid Social
The brief Cade Street Nursery is a family business based in Heathfield, East Sussex, and they have been growing plants and flowers there since the 1980s.
“Polis Paralela responded to the challenge of the targets set within the project and really got behind our business. Targets were exceeded and this resulted in a good uplift in sales.” &amp;mdash; Rob Honeysett, Cade Street Nursery Sales &amp;amp; Planning Manager  Polis Paralela had previously developed a website for them in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 examples of digital marketing &amp; PR tactics used throughout history</title>
      <link>/thinks/4-examples-of-digital-marketing-pr-tactics-used-throughout-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 09:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/4-examples-of-digital-marketing-pr-tactics-used-throughout-history/</guid>
      <description>History’s cool.
Digital marketing is cool.
Can I haphazardly combine the two together?
Maybe!
Here are four occurrences throughout human history that I think reflect some key pillars of modern digital marketing and PR, as well as some useful lessons we can learn from them.
SEO – Welsh village changes name Lanff…Lanfairgwillygo…Llanfairpwlllogegllant… The vast majority of people in the UK are aware of that place in Anglesey, Wales that has the most mind-bogglingly Welsh name in creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This one special trick will get you more customers!</title>
      <link>/thinks/google-reviews-local-seo-factors-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 11:26:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/google-reviews-local-seo-factors-2017/</guid>
      <description>The definitive guide to Local Search Ranking Factors has recently been updated&amp;hellip;and I wanted to share one thing in particular:
Here’s a graph showing a load of positive ranking factors for Google Business listings. Those are the ones that show up at the top of page 1 in the map bit. They’re ordered from the strongest on the left downwards.
All the yellow ones are to do with GOOGLE REVIEWS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BrightonSEO key takeaways</title>
      <link>/thinks/brightonseo-key-takeways/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 09:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/brightonseo-key-takeways/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this month I attended my fourth edition BrightonSEO conference - another great day that left me walking back up to Brighton station with my head brimming with ideas!
Once again I find myself reflecting on how incredibly fortunate it is that this fantastic resource is just a few stops on the train away. People come by plane, train and automobile to what is now Europe&amp;rsquo;s largest SEO conference, so being able to have a bit of a lie-in and still be there for the 10am start is an absolute luxury!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#BrightonSEO hits the Brighton Centre</title>
      <link>/thinks/brightonseo-hits-brighton-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 16:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/brightonseo-hits-brighton-centre/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday saw another Brighton SEO conference take place, and I was lucky to once again attend after my first visit in April.
This time it was held at its new home at the Brighton Centre - a testament to how popular the event has gotten since 2011, and a far cry from the back room of a pub where the first one was held!
Around three thousand search marketers were in attendance to take in a whole host of talks from an array of industry experts, and it once again proved to be a valuable experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of having a digital strategy</title>
      <link>/thinks/importance-digital-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 08:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/importance-digital-strategy/</guid>
      <description>In a previous blog post I explained what digital disruption is, and how the landscape for marketers has been under a rapid evolution in recent times with the advent of new technology.
With this in mind, it&amp;rsquo;s a great idea for your company to have a proper digital strategy documented.
With the scope of digital marketing getting wider, integrating it into overall business strategies can appear to be a mammoth task to undertake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A brief guide to using Pokemon Go for your local business</title>
      <link>/thinks/a-brief-guide-to-using-pokemon-go-for-your-local-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 13:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/a-brief-guide-to-using-pokemon-go-for-your-local-business/</guid>
      <description>Not heard of Pokemon Go? Where have you been?!
Since its release, the augmented reality-based game has taken the world by absolute storm. It&amp;rsquo;s been a constant trending topic on Twitter for about a week now (yes, even throughout all the political guff going on) and has seen Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s share price rise by a mammoth 86 per cent!
And, on a worldwide scale, this massive dose of 90&amp;rsquo;s nostalgia is seeing more active daily users than Twitter and WhatsApp, and even more engagement than Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How long does it take to rank a new website using SEO?</title>
      <link>/thinks/ranking-a-new-website-using-seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 09:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/ranking-a-new-website-using-seo/</guid>
      <description>So you&amp;rsquo;ve got a brand spanking new website, and you&amp;rsquo;re now ready to release it out into the wild and start attracting traffic to it. But what should you realistically be expecting in terms of results?
It can be a bit daunting if you&amp;rsquo;re not sure exactly what to expect from your online marketing efforts. The fabled Google search algorithm is a mysterious creature; there&amp;rsquo;s no &amp;lsquo;magic formula&amp;rsquo; to it, and it&amp;rsquo;s constantly evolving and keeping digital marketers on their toes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What on earth is &#39;dark social&#39; anyway?</title>
      <link>/thinks/earth-dark-social-anyway/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 13:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/earth-dark-social-anyway/</guid>
      <description>Research was released last month showing that a gargantuan 77 per cent of content is being shared via &amp;lsquo;dark social&amp;rsquo; channels.
For social media marketers, that&amp;rsquo;s massive. The huge amount of dark social sharing shows how people are now consuming online media – switching from channel to channel over many devices per day.
But as the title suggests, what the heck is &amp;lsquo;dark social&amp;rsquo;?
Essentially, it&amp;rsquo;s visits to your website that comes from the sharing of content on social platforms that aren&amp;rsquo;t easily quantified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing 101 - the 4Cs of the Marketing Mix</title>
      <link>/thinks/marketing-101-4cs-marketing-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 10:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/marketing-101-4cs-marketing-mix/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s get right back to basics. What is &amp;lsquo;marketing&amp;rsquo; anyway?
Generally, it&amp;rsquo;s a means of getting people or businesses to buy into whatever product or service you&amp;rsquo;re offering.
From a more academic viewpoint, the Chartered Institute of Marketing say that marketing is &amp;ldquo;the management process responsible for identifying, anticipating and satisfying customer requirements profitably.&amp;rdquo;
But how do you decide what to do to your marketing to try and leverage extra success from your efforts?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know your limits! Changes to Google &amp; Twitter imminent</title>
      <link>/thinks/know-limits-changes-google-twitter-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/know-limits-changes-google-twitter-way/</guid>
      <description>Remember the turn of the year when it was rumoured that Twitter was upping its limit from 140 characters to a whopping 10,000?
Thank goodness that didn&amp;rsquo;t happen! The think-pieces were in full flow for the first couple of weeks of January, such was the drastic nature of the supposed changes. But after some backlash from a number of users, the idea was quietly dropped.
There&amp;rsquo;s a small level of satisfaction when you manage to cram everything into the strict limitations of the platform; it&amp;rsquo;s the brevity that keeps Twitter fast-paced and relevant by encouraging people to tweet in the moment the essence of what they want to communicate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 ridiculously cool things you can do with targeted Facebook Ads</title>
      <link>/thinks/cool-facebook-ad-experiments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 15:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/cool-facebook-ad-experiments/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s something that digital marketeers are having to think about more and more. When does personalisation cross over into breach of privacy?
People have pumped so much personal information into the digital sphere as social media has become an intrinsic part of their daily lives.
Cookies, browsing history, location services - it&amp;rsquo;s really no surprise that the very best marketing organisations utilise big data, automation, segmentation and personalisation to deliver the best and most relevant content to its target audiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local SEO @ Polis Paralela&#39;s local SEO conference - BrightonSEO</title>
      <link>/thinks/brighton-seo-how-to-be-a-local-seo-jedi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 14:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/brighton-seo-how-to-be-a-local-seo-jedi/</guid>
      <description>I had my first experience of the amazing Brighton SEO conference on Friday – seeing as how I&amp;rsquo;ve lived down the road from Brighton most of my life, it’s pretty poor form that I&amp;rsquo;d never been to the event before&amp;hellip;
The day proved to be incredibly valuable on the whole and the Brighton Dome was absolutely packed with digital marketers from all over the UK and beyond. In fact, there were so many it was announced on the day that the next edition will take place at the much larger Brighton Centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why SEO is a bit like cycling</title>
      <link>/thinks/why-seo-is-like-cycling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 15:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/why-seo-is-like-cycling/</guid>
      <description>In a previous post I dropped an analogy at the end likening the practice of search engine optimisation to that of top-level cycling.
No, not that those who do it do so with a helping hand from a range of performance enhancing drugs&amp;hellip;it was actually to do with the philosophy of David Brailsford, former performance director of British Cycling and now manager of the very successful Team Sky:
 &amp;ldquo;The whole principle came from the idea that if you broke down everything you could think of that goes into riding a bike, and then improved it by 1%, you will get a significant increase when you put them all together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things Polis Paralela likes this week - 15 April 2016</title>
      <link>/thinks/things-tomango-likes-week-15-april-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 14:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/things-tomango-likes-week-15-april-2016/</guid>
      <description>A quick round-up of the week as we pick out some of the highlights from the world of Brand, Web, and Online Marketing.
BRAND AND DESIGN: Domino&amp;rsquo;s unveil new packaging design Everyone knows that there&amp;rsquo;s never any point in just buying one Dominos – Two for Tuesdays and other such offers mean that 96% of pizzas sold in the UK by the chain go in pairs.
Designers JKR Global were given the brief to revamp the Domino&amp;rsquo;s brand packaging and produced this simple yet effective design, turning the Dominos logo into the packaging itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local SEO: a 10-minute guide to help your business</title>
      <link>/thinks/local-seo-a-brief-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 10:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/local-seo-a-brief-guide/</guid>
      <description>Local SEO - what is it?
In an nutshell, local SEO is the process of trying to get your business noticed by people in your area conducting relevant searches.
Why is local SEO more important than ever?
Go to Google and type in ‘cinema’, ‘petrol station’, or ‘pizza’…and you&amp;rsquo;ll notice that it&amp;rsquo;ll show up with a map with pins dropped on the nearest examples of where you can find those things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to write better copy for your website, Part 2 - make it all about your reader</title>
      <link>/thinks/how-to-write-better-copy-for-your-website-part-2-make-it-all-about-your-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 15:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/how-to-write-better-copy-for-your-website-part-2-make-it-all-about-your-reader/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Steve, and I give my customers their weekends back.&amp;rdquo;
With his opening gambit, this guy had my attention. And he was the only person I&amp;rsquo;d met that morning who really had.
The exhausting pastime of speed networking Have you ever been speed networking? It&amp;rsquo;s like speed dating, but for businesses.
Around 50 nervous-looking people get split into two groups, with one half stationed at tables scattered around a hotel conference room, and the other half are on the move, spending two minutes talking to each new &amp;ldquo;partner&amp;rdquo; before a whistle blows (I kid you not), and moving on to their next potential new-best-friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to write better copy for your website, Part 1 - writing for a lower reading age</title>
      <link>/thinks/how-to-write-better-copy-for-your-website-part-1-writing-for-a-lower-reading-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 16:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/how-to-write-better-copy-for-your-website-part-1-writing-for-a-lower-reading-age/</guid>
      <description>Writing copy for your website is hard. Writing good copy is even harder.
A common misconception about writing good copy is that it must be lavish, flowing and full of impressive words; and many writers find this prospect intimidating.
 The best copy is easy to read
 But it turns out that if you want your copy to be more widely read - by more people and in more detail - you need to simplify it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evergreen content saves you time and makes you money</title>
      <link>/thinks/evergreen-content-saves-time-makes-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2015 08:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/evergreen-content-saves-time-makes-money/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to let you in on a little secret that will help your online marketing campaign be successful AND save you time into the bargain.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you all about Evergreen Content.
What is evergreen content? So what is this magical ingredient that makes your content marketing campaign so successful?
Well it&amp;rsquo;s nothing to do with trees, and it&amp;rsquo;s nothing to do with colours. Evergreen content refers to an article (usually a blog post) that doesn&amp;rsquo;t age or date quickly, or at least isn&amp;rsquo;t short-lived; it stays relevant for a long time - it stays &amp;ldquo;evergreen&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to choose a good SEO company (and what to avoid)</title>
      <link>/thinks/how-to-choose-a-good-seo-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 17:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/how-to-choose-a-good-seo-company/</guid>
      <description>We talk to a lot of new clients about their online marketing requirements. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the things we do, after all. Unfortunately we often hear about bad experiences with other online marketing companies that puts people off the whole thing. Once bitten, twice shy and all that.
So, in this post we&amp;rsquo;re going to tell you about some of the most common warning signs to look out for that indicate you should steer clear, and show you how to choose a GOOD SEO company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 5 secrets to keeping your customers truly happy</title>
      <link>/thinks/5-secrets-to-keeping-your-customers-truly-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 15:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/5-secrets-to-keeping-your-customers-truly-happy/</guid>
      <description>In the late summer of 2010, two young entrepreneurs called Hayley Barna and Katie Beauchamp came up with the idea of making money from selling small sample-size cosmetics - mini-tubes of mascara and baubles of liquid blush - often tossed in to beauty store shopping bags as freebies.
Today Birchbox has over 400,000 customers paying £10 each month to receive a goodie bag of samples in the post - and the customers don&amp;rsquo;t even get to choose what they get.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging made easy - an idiot&#39;s guide</title>
      <link>/thinks/blogging-made-easy-idiots-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 11:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/blogging-made-easy-idiots-guide/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably already heard a lot about the benefits of writing a blog. The vast majority of new clients I talk to are aware it&amp;rsquo;s something they should be doing. But in our already busy lives, the prospect of having to squeeze in yet one more thing can be so daunting it prevents it ever getting off the ground. So this blog post is for all you busy bods out there; 6 steps to follow so you can enjoy the benefits of blogging with the minimum amount of effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is email marketing still effective? £4,040 in 20 minutes says the answer is yes</title>
      <link>/thinks/email-marketing-still-effective-4040-20-minutes-says-answer-yes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2014 10:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/email-marketing-still-effective-4040-20-minutes-says-answer-yes/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some hard evidence that email marketing works and can bring you a significant return on your investment.
A few weeks ago I spent about 20 minutes composing and sending our monthly email out to our clients. This simple bit of marketing immediately generated £4,040 of sales. Let me tell you how I did it&amp;hellip;
Every month I write a couple of blog posts for the Polis Paralela website, usually about a particular area of our business that I think might be of interest to either our clients or prospective customers looking for a brand and web agency like ours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s your tipple?  Finding the right online marketing mix</title>
      <link>/thinks/whats-tipple-finding-right-online-marketing-mix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 13:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/whats-tipple-finding-right-online-marketing-mix/</guid>
      <description>In the same way that Del Boy isn&amp;rsquo;t likely to settle for a Vodka Martini and you won&amp;rsquo;t see James Bond diving into a Pina Colada, there&amp;rsquo;s no such thing as a one-size-fits-all online marketing campaign.
There are lots of different ingredients that can make up your online marketing cocktail and you need to judge the quantities of each to get something that&amp;rsquo;s just right for you.
For some, pay-per-click and good ol&amp;rsquo; search engine optimisation (SEO) might be the dominant flavours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More than just a digital marketing agency</title>
      <link>/thinks/more-than-just-a-digital-marketing-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 16:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/more-than-just-a-digital-marketing-agency/</guid>
      <description>With the Polis Paralela summer party just over two weeks away, we reflect on the different backgrounds and businesses of our guests and the wide range of services we now provide for them.
Before we merged to become Polis Paralela, both Blue Planet and Jupiter Colour were formed as website design companies, but now we&amp;rsquo;re about so much more than that. Our &amp;ldquo;vision&amp;rdquo; for Polis Paralela was to be the best brand identity design, website design and online marketing company in Sussex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to write brilliant website content</title>
      <link>/thinks/how-to-write-brilliant-website-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 11:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/how-to-write-brilliant-website-content/</guid>
      <description>Well-crafted website content is the key to increasing web traffic and more importantly, getting enquiries and making sales.
In this article we look at 6 top tips for creating brilliant website content.
1. Content is king Everyone loves fresh content – search engines and customers alike. If you do one thing on your website, it&amp;rsquo;s well worth spending your time regularly creating new, interesting content for your website, which is why blogs are so popular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When is the best time to send your marketing emails?</title>
      <link>/thinks/the-best-times-to-send-your-marketing-emails/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 10:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinks/the-best-times-to-send-your-marketing-emails/</guid>
      <description>Mid-morning to coincide with coffee break? Lunchtime? At the end of the afternoon when people are starting to think about going home? When IS the best time to send your marketing emails?
Research has been carried out by a leading email marketing company into what is the best time of day to send out your beautifully crafted HTML emails. The results might surprise you; for example, B2B marketers frequently preferring to open their mails after office hours and consumers choosing first thing in the morning to check theirs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>