<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brand on Polis Paralela</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/categories/brand/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brand on Polis Paralela</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 16:10:50 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//localhost:1313/thinks/categories/brand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How rebranding my business scared the shit out of me</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/how-rebranding-my-business-scared-the-shit-out-of-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 16:10:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/how-rebranding-my-business-scared-the-shit-out-of-me/</guid>
      <description>There are times in your business life when certain things stay the same for a long time.
You tread the path you’ve chosen, working in a way that’s familiar and well-honed, and you feel comfortable.
Then there are times when massive changes happen.
The last twelve months for me has definitely been the latter.
The Rut In January 2018, Polis Paralela was five years old. The business had always been stable and profitable, and we’d enjoyed steady if unspectacular growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Brand Identity and why is it important to my business?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/brand-identity-important-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 10:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/brand-identity-important-business/</guid>
      <description>What is brand identity? Your brand identity is how you want to portray your business to your customers, and includes how you choose your business name, the design of your logo, the colours and shapes or graphics you use, and the type of language you use (your “tone of voice”).
Brand identity is different to brand image, which is the result of these efforts. I.e. a successful brand identity translates into a positive brand image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to buy design for your business to get maximum ROI</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/how-to-buy-design-for-your-business-to-get-maximum-roi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 08:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/how-to-buy-design-for-your-business-to-get-maximum-roi/</guid>
      <description>We know that investing in design is a good thing.
Research has shown that for every £1 invested in design, businesses can expect over £20 in increased revenues.
But how do you go about buying design?
The old-fashioned way, and why it’s flawed as a process I don’t know exactly when it became standard practice, but the way most businesses find an agency to help them with their brand, website or any other part of their marketing, is usually as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When branding matters - part #316</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/branding-matters-part-316/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 09:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/branding-matters-part-316/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s one of my favourite stories about how your branding&amp;rsquo;s very important to customers - and often in ways you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t expect.
One Wednesday morning, a junior member of the Customer Services team took a phone call at the Macclesfield store of renowned department store Arighi Bianchi.
&amp;ldquo;Good morning, this is Arighi Bianchi. How can I help you?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I want to make a complaint.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m sorry to hear that madam, but I can certainly help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens when you self-diagnose</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/happens-self-diagnose/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 14:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/happens-self-diagnose/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a couple of great stories about stupidity.
The first story concerns a friend who&amp;rsquo;s a GP.
One day a few years ago, a middle-aged woman turned up at her surgery feeling lousy. She had no energy, bad headaches and her limbs were aching.
She was convinced she had Lyme disease and proceeded to instruct the doctor to prescribe her the antibiotic amoxicillin.
Of course, my doctor friend insisted on a proper consultation and suspected the lady probably just had flu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a brand design brief - download our template</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/how-to-create-a-brand-design-brief/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 15:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/how-to-create-a-brand-design-brief/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s well known that having a strong brand identity can make a massive difference to any business.
Having the right brand identity helps you:
 Get more of the customers you want Keep your best customers for longer Charge the right price for what you sell Stand apart from your competitors  Read about how Agon Systems tripled its turnover in three years to £5 million by investing in its brand identity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why it doesn&#39;t matter if you don&#39;t like your own brand identity</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/doesnt-matter-dont-like-brand-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 11:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/doesnt-matter-dont-like-brand-identity/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;But I don&amp;rsquo;t like green. Can we try it in another colour?&amp;rdquo;
This was what a client said to us, a couple of years ago, when we presented our concept for his new brand identity.
It seems like an understandable response and a reasonable request, right?
The client was in financial services, and was setting up a new business venture. He&amp;rsquo;d come to us because he had nothing - no brand, no printed collateral, no website, not even a name - and he wanted to give his start-up the best chance of being a success by investing what was (for him) quite a bit of money in the development of his brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Clever Logos with Hidden Meaning</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/seven-clever-logos-hidden-meaning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 10:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/seven-clever-logos-hidden-meaning/</guid>
      <description>The biggest and best companies in the world can spend millions of pounds trying to find that perfect image to represent their brand.
There&amp;rsquo;s thousands of examples out there, but some stand out thanks to small factors behind their design that elevate them from a standard logo to something a bit special.
1. Sony Vaio A perfect example of a logo that has an ingenious element to it, this one for Sony&amp;rsquo;s now-discontinued range of Vaio laptops uses the letter of the brand name to cleverly show the integration of the analogue and digital data transfer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big brand impact from a brochure</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/big-brand-impact-brochure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 13:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/big-brand-impact-brochure/</guid>
      <description>With the new website now live, we continued the brand rollout for the Concept Tag with the creation of a new brochure.
The brochure was created to promote the Concept Tag; the “World’s most secure EAS Tag”. This revolutionary new product from Agon Systems eliminates illicit tag removal and is proven to reduce losses by 66%.
By obtaining a detailed brief from the client it became clear the brochure had to reinforce the key values of the product; quality, reliability and durability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things Polis Paralela likes this week - 15 April 2016</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/things-tomango-likes-week-15-april-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 14:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/things-tomango-likes-week-15-april-2016/</guid>
      <description>A quick round-up of the week as we pick out some of the highlights from the world of Brand, Web, and Online Marketing.
BRAND AND DESIGN: Domino&amp;rsquo;s unveil new packaging design Everyone knows that there&amp;rsquo;s never any point in just buying one Dominos – Two for Tuesdays and other such offers mean that 96% of pizzas sold in the UK by the chain go in pairs.
Designers JKR Global were given the brief to revamp the Domino&amp;rsquo;s brand packaging and produced this simple yet effective design, turning the Dominos logo into the packaging itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand identity for Sussex payroll specialist</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/brand-identity-for-sussex-payroll-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 08:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/brand-identity-for-sussex-payroll-specialist/</guid>
      <description>Ever wondered what the difference is between a logo and a brand identity?
Last week we completed a new brand identity for a Sussex payroll specialist based just up the road in nearby Uckfield.
Our client - Pay Assist We were approached by Pay Assist - an outsourced payroll services company based in Uckfield - in January to design and develop the brand identity.
It was clear from the outset that Pay Assist was a client that didn&amp;rsquo;t just need a logo throwing together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 5 secrets to keeping your customers truly happy</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/5-secrets-to-keeping-your-customers-truly-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 15:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/5-secrets-to-keeping-your-customers-truly-happy/</guid>
      <description>In the late summer of 2010, two young entrepreneurs called Hayley Barna and Katie Beauchamp came up with the idea of making money from selling small sample-size cosmetics - mini-tubes of mascara and baubles of liquid blush - often tossed in to beauty store shopping bags as freebies.
Today Birchbox has over 400,000 customers paying £10 each month to receive a goodie bag of samples in the post - and the customers don&amp;rsquo;t even get to choose what they get.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand identity design for Brighton gourmet food retailer comes to life</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/brand-identity-design-brighton-gourmet-food-retailer-comes-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 16:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/brand-identity-design-brighton-gourmet-food-retailer-comes-life/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s little in my professional life that gives me greater satisfaction than seeing a brand identity that we&amp;rsquo;ve created come to life. Seeing Polis Paralela&amp;rsquo;s work in print or on the high street gives me a lovely little warm glow inside. Last week I was fortunate enough to see our client&amp;rsquo;s brand hard at work in a newly opened gourmet food deli in Brighton; the new home of Sage &amp;amp; Relish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How a new brand identity positioned Agon Systems ahead of its competitors</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/agon-systems-new-brand-identity-positioned-ahead-competitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2014 10:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/agon-systems-new-brand-identity-positioned-ahead-competitors/</guid>
      <description>How can a strong brand identity set you apart from your competitors and win you more business? Take a look at the work we&amp;rsquo;ve recently done for Agon Systems and see for yourself.
Background &amp;amp; history Agon Systems is a manufacturer of Electronic Article Surveillance (EAS) equipment based near Biel, in Switzerland.
You&amp;rsquo;ve probably seen and walked past EAS equipment hundreds of times in your life; thousands if you&amp;rsquo;re a keen shopper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why asking us to do a creative pitch or speculative design is wrong</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/asking-us-creative-pitch-speculative-design-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2013 17:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/asking-us-creative-pitch-speculative-design-wrong/</guid>
      <description>Increasingly we&amp;rsquo;re being invited by prospective clients to &amp;ldquo;pitch&amp;rdquo; for their project. This isn&amp;rsquo;t the same as providing a quote or tendering for a job; this is where we&amp;rsquo;re being asked to create designs based on a written brief, to present to the client in the hope they&amp;rsquo;ll choose us. This old-skool practice is usually known as a &amp;ldquo;creative pitch&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;speculative design&amp;rdquo; and we think it&amp;rsquo;s wrong. Here we explain why.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jumping on the brandwagon - don&#39;t slag off a new brand when you don&#39;t know the brief</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/jumping-brandwagon-important-understand-brief-new-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 18:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/jumping-brandwagon-important-understand-brief-new-brand/</guid>
      <description>This week, following a swift u-turn after a fans&amp;rsquo; backlash, Everton Football Club launched its NEW new brand identity. This is the latest example in the last few months of a high profile company re-brand that has drawn criticism from both the design community and the brand&amp;rsquo;s own customers.
But it&amp;rsquo;s not right to just dismiss a new brand without knowing the brief. How can you judge the success of a rebrand if you don&amp;rsquo;t know what it&amp;rsquo;s trying to achieve?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brand design for Sussex commercial property letting agents</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/brand-design-for-sussex-commercial-property-letting-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 15:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/brand-design-for-sussex-commercial-property-letting-agents/</guid>
      <description>Oldfield Smith is a new commercial letting agent based in Uckfield, established by Richard Oldfield and Bernard Smith. Richard and Bernard approached *Polis Paralela* in the spring of 2013 to ask us to develop their brand identity and website.
Brand design brief Their brand identity needed to express Oldfield Smith&amp;rsquo;s quality of service, combining the highest professional standards with a warm, open and honest service. The image they want to portray is approachable, honest, professional, results-driven and enthusiastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More than just a digital marketing agency</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/more-than-just-a-digital-marketing-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 16:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/more-than-just-a-digital-marketing-agency/</guid>
      <description>With the Polis Paralela summer party just over two weeks away, we reflect on the different backgrounds and businesses of our guests and the wide range of services we now provide for them.
Before we merged to become Polis Paralela, both Blue Planet and Jupiter Colour were formed as website design companies, but now we&amp;rsquo;re about so much more than that. Our &amp;ldquo;vision&amp;rdquo; for Polis Paralela was to be the best brand identity design, website design and online marketing company in Sussex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate identity for Sussex Letting Shop</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/corporate-identity-for-sussex-letting-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 09:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/corporate-identity-for-sussex-letting-shop/</guid>
      <description>When we got a call from Wendy at Geneva Investment Group in Hove asking about designing a new website, little did we know that we would be helping them shape their corporate identity as well&amp;hellip;
In October 2012, we received an email from Wendy at Geneva Investment Group asking us to talk to them about designing and developing a new website for them. Geneva Investment Group is one of the biggest private landlords in Brighton and Hove in Sussex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polis Paralela&#39;s new brand identity</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/thinks/tomangos-new-brand-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2012 17:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/thinks/tomangos-new-brand-identity/</guid>
      <description>Following on from the announcement of the arrival of Polis Paralela in our previous blog post, we are now able to reveal the new brand identity for the company.
In this post, we wanted to take the opportunity to not only show you the final brand identity design, but also to describe in detail the process we followed to achieve the end result. This is the same process that we follow for our clients, so we thought it might be interesting for you to see behind the scenes of how a new brand identity is developed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>